JOHN GARZON

100 Golden Isles Dr. Hallandale, FL 33009 954 - 681 - 3241 | gajohn511@gmail.com

https://whispering-wildwood-43957.herokuapp.com/

SUMMARY

Software Developer with 6+ years experience in ASP.Net / Full Stack., experienced with telerik controls. Front-End Developer 6+ years using CSS & JavaScript. Experienced using frameworks such as Bootstrap, JQuery, Angular, and MongoDB. Developed an aptitude for MEAN Stack. Seeking a team oriented developer position, with dynamic and competitive projects in .NET/Full-Stack and Front-End development.

EXPERIENCE

Broadway Across America Pompano FL — Software Engineer

Feb 2014 - Dec 2016

Engineer to our ticket sales RESTful web services, consumed by the public domain, using .net & JSON. Team member to the front-end ninjas, developed an in-house admin application for ticket sales and administration, using full stack, Agil, and SDLC. Keeping our applications up to date, version pushes, enhancements, and bug fixes. Lots of front-end development: Entity Framework, Bootstrap3, HTML5, CSS3, refactoring, and clean coding.

http://www.broadway.com

First Service Residential Inc. Dania Beach FL — Software Developer

Nov 2008 - Feb 2014

I was solely responsible of the legacy iteration of Connect titled Connect3 when I first came on board, developed in ASP and MySQL, supporting and maintenance of the system for 3+ years. Also a developer to our SaaS application - FSR Community website, developed in .NET, specialized in bug fixes, enhancement, and QA. I was then part of the team to help develop and migrate connect 3 to Connect4 (next iteration enterprise system SaaS software developed in .net 4.0 with telerik) to production, following all phases of SDLC. http://fsrsouth.myconnect.cc (Connect 4) https://dcmetro.fsrconnect.com

EDUCATION

F.I.U Miami FL — Bachelors of Information Technology

Sep 2004 - May 2008

Pace University, New York NY—M.I.S. Sep 2000 - Jun 2003